(Isabella:)Rajesh, this is so sweet,
(Isabella:)but you... you know I'm working.
(Raj:)That's why I already
cleaned up in here
(Raj:)and all the other rooms
in the hall.
(Isabella:)Well, I suppose that gives me
a little time.
Oh, please sit!
(Raj:)I tried to cook you
a meal from your homeland.
(Isabella:)Oh, really?
(Isabella:)You made Cuban food?
(Raj:)That depends-- do they have
Mexican food in Cuba?
Now, when he said "make a baby"
(Penny:)is it possible he
meant out of Legos?
(Amy:)No. He was explicit.
(Amy:)Needlessly
and freakishly explicit.
(Leonard:)Why does he need a baby?
(Leonard:)He's already hairless
and smells like talcum powder.
(Penny:)Could you two really
have some sort of
(Penny:)super-intelligent child?
(Amy:)Well, there is
a genetic component,
(Amy:)but that doesn't
guarantee anything.
(Leonard:)That's true.
Sheldon's father
(Leonard:)once picked a fight
with a cactus.